Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/viveky259 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Gitlab

Object-Oriented Programming (OOP)

GitHub

Certifications

AWS Amplify: Open Source Foundation Contributor

The Complete Flutter App Development Course for Android, iOS

Vivek Yadav

Google Developer Expert for Flutter and Dart | Building TATA Neu App | Co-Organizer @FlutterIndia and @MumbaiFlutter Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

Summary

Things where I can help: Flutter, Firebase, Android(Java, Kotlin), NodeJS, Hasura

Currently: Building Mobile ecosystem Flutter @Tata Digital

I have experience in Android and NodeJS development for more than 4 years. and Flutter for more than 5 years

Development in Flutter is on the way. I have mentored SIH2018, ACMWH2018, and SIH2019.

I am a proud participant of SMART INDIA HACKATHON (the World's biggest hackathon).

The project for the hackathon was automation in the preparation of the tender document. The project was completed in 36 hours. It was held on the 1st of April.

Experience

Tata Digital

Dev Lead May 2023 - Present (1 year 4 months)

Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

I am working with Tata Digital, a future-ready company that focuses on creating consumer-centric, high-engagement digital products. I will be working on the Tata Neu app.

ITM Skills University
Board of Advisors
August 2023 - Present (1 year 1 month)

Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

Contribution towards the curriculum for commitment to excellence in education.

Google for Startups

Mentor

May 2022 - Present (2 years 4 months)

India

Google Developer Experts

Google Developer Expert for Flutter and Dart

July 2021 - Present (3 years 2 months)

Tata Neu Skills

Mentor

December 2023 - Present (9 months)

Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

Flutter Mumbai

Organizer

December 2019 - Present (4 years 9 months)

Mumbai Area, India

Medium

Writer

November 2018 - Present (5 years 10 months)

United States

Flutter India

Organizer

May 2020 - Present (4 years 4 months)

Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

Creating events at Flutter India with every Flutter Communities in India.

StringsWay Tech

Artist

February 2018 - Present (6 years 7 months)

Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

ZestMoney

2 years 1 month

SDE 3 - Lead Mobile Developer

April 2022 - April 2023 (1 year 1 month)

India

1. Working on delivering the mobile app to 5M users in India

- 2. Working on creating a better experience for the mobile app
- 3. Building Mobile Team
- 4. Scaling app for millions of users
- 5. Making it accessible for millions to upgrade their finance capability

SDE 2- Senior Flutter Developer

April 2021 - April 2023 (2 years 1 month)

India

Leading a team of 6 people to deliver ZestMoney's iOS app build in Flutter

HighLevel

Sr. Flutter Dev

September 2020 - April 2021 (8 months)

United States

Senior Mobile Application Developer @HighLevel | Co-organiser

@FlutterMumbai, @Flutter India | Speaker & Mentor | Business development

@StringswayTech

Rirev

Flutter Dev

December 2019 - September 2020 (10 months)

Mumbai Area, India

Flutter Dev @ Rirev

ICICI Lombard

Flutter Developer Consultant

May 2019 - December 2019 (8 months)

Mumbai Area, India

ICICI Lombard is a great company and it was great to work with them as a consultant for Flutter, Android, and Firebase too. I had a great team there. I participated in ICICI Lombard Hackathon where I was responsible for developing and maintaining three flutter applications. I had exposure to real-time project management, development and iterations. Thanks ICICI Lombard for lifting up my career.

FitPhilia Solutions Private Limited Software Engineer August 2017 - May 2019 (1 year 10 months)

Andheri

FitPhilia is an Ideal company for me with great leaders and team. My transition from a noob programmer to a professional programmer took place in FitPhilia

under the guidance of leaders of the company. This was a place where I learned how startup works in real world.

IlexSquare
Python Developer
July 2017 - August 2017 (2 months)
Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

Learned python and built simple ERP using web and python

bebitz flanges IT intern August 2016 - September 2016 (2 months) ERP software learner

Education

Haji Jamaluddin Thim TrustTheem College of Engineering B.E., Computer Engineering (2013 - 2017)

New English School 12th, HSC with computer Science

Pancham English High School 10th, SSC